Prashant Paliwal is taking the initiative and we will
talk to you on our show about town planners
for policy. If you are searching for town plan or
nifty, or you
want to know what all products your print out plan
gives and what are the factors that are considered in an
insurance policy, then in this video we will
answer all your questions.
We will also discuss whether there is such a town
planning for quality which provides
for dialysis in case of kidney failure, or
gives you monthly pension in case of complete blindness. So let's start with
insurance problems. Differently
based policies are not covered by this
insurance policy.
After this, we will discuss apart from food, clothing
and shelter, there is a fourth requirement which is
called elevating from a
good education generation pays off. Similarly, these clothing
shopping jobs also change the generation.
If no one survives in this world,
a son passes away, a father passes away, a husband passes away,
social status passes away. We
cannot do all these things in America, but we have income.  There is a
part which can be recovered by
way of life insurance emotional life this
human life playlist let us talk to you no
one in your family can take your place
my emotions the productive power that I have while living with my family
cannot be colored but
my given life is first in tempo pension
value medium calling it can be covered there are
two formulas to call it
income replacement method and
Spencer placement here I
Friday daughter - your age add into any
expense from inflation insisted your
insurance advisor that this should be done you
second simple formula is
sixteen times your annual income and the third even
simpler formula is how much amount
tubelight loop if you
go out of the house for a month then you fill your one month
provision ration and water if
you go out for six months then you leave
electricity for everyone if you come to know today
that after today you are not going to come back to your home then
how much money do you want to leave for your family that is
you have to decide i.e.
phone number to or mathematically  I am explaining
this on my own,
all this is just a meeting, it is 1 lakh rupees per month, I am 14 years old,
if I
take life insurance of 2 crores,
then something like Bumrah, my family will get up to 2 crores,
now even banks are making profit from 12 crores,
or you can
take an insurance pension plan of any company, it is simple and they
want, then 1 lakh rupees per month will keep
coming to my house, that is, whatever was
coming to my house during my life,
half of it will come to my house after my death, if I earn 100 crores,
this is about
my expenses, my kitchen
expenses are approximately 15000,
house rent goes up to 15000, school expenses of both the children
together amount to 15000, if
I call all this then every person whose salary is less than Rs. 10000 has to spend Rs. 75 to 80 thousand
rupees,
now he should not buy any such
thing on which my family can compromise
and  What is the need to do this if
after my death my family gets 1 lakh rupees per month,
you will have to compromise a bit, they will
live with their heads held high, they will
not have to beg for anything, if I die then it is a
very good thing my family will get
2 crore rupees and 1 lakh women will
start getting pension throughout the film lifestyle,
what will happen now if an accident happens and
I am not killed and I have decided,
God forbid both of them come and go, I will be in a
wheelchair for the rest of my life, I
cannot earn money, in such a situation will my Nifty do
some work for me or will any of my major body
organs be, both my kidneys have failed, it
depends on the
meaning and its policies,
my lifestyle increases, I
clean Punjabi in lakhs,
tomorrow the medium will be above 5 lakhs, then I will
spend 4.5 lakh rupees, my income will do
with it, but my Health Web did
not ignore that my wealth will increase but it will
decrease, after Sandals for,
any company will do it for me today and
setting is practically not  If it is not possible
then can it be possible that my phone or that company
automatically increases my mood every year?
Here I am talking about a man
who gets annual increment at the Harshal time.
In the year 2009 his salary was 15000,
then in 2020, that is, after 20 years, his salary was
lakhs per month and if here I understand that he keeps getting annual
increment then 2,040 rupees will be given along with
it, then it will happen to us.
We often get insurance of one crore or two crores, with
that we can be stress
free on the road. Will this one crore
insurance policy 826 system option be there
and after 20 years who will give me justice?
Then should such a policy not be taken today?
For this, contact comes which is called
Sampoorna Suraksha Kanoon, only such
insurance policies which give you life
insurance coverage
and disability cover, you will get the
heart of defense and your insurance
also increases annually, with this the customer will get it and it is possible,
apart from this there will be life insurance coverage, if there is
accidental disability,
you will get it in the first place, that major fit will be done.
Bypass surgery will be required like
share for kidney failure, you will get the last benefit of
your age, protection brighter is also
added in it that if I get
accidentally disabled and cannot
earn money, then I will start getting monthly pension
and every year my insurance
policy will commode brother and
listen to pipe pipe 20%, so here I have taken a simple cardamom
policy, LIC's simple endowment
plan number 814, all this
protection is possible in this also for just ₹100 a day,
after I took it, I get the income up to
25 lakhs, if I die,
I will run wearing accidental death cover, in case of
accidental disability, I will
start getting monthly pension, if any
difficulty arises, I will get up to 10 lakhs on this, I
can get treatment accordingly and every year the life will increase
from these thieves and the policy will
match,
after 30 years I will get double the amount back
which I had set, now because here I was
getting maturity, so
you will get Rs. 100 a day  Information Delhi might seem a little less,
now I don't get maturity in it,
talk about that friend, marks and pure
report you wish to keep, you do
n't get sweet bread back, here I have taken a
term plan of Rs 1 crore, the first one
I had taken was the same positive Upender
riders and that policy was customized,
here I am talking about three different
policies, I have taken a minimum insurance of Rs 1 crore
from a life insurance company,
I have taken a mediclaim of Rs 10 lakh from a health
insurance company and I have taken a
personal accidental plan of Rs 50 lakh, this covers 20 minimum
accidental cases
and by combining these things the deduction came out to be the same
and the neighborhood is ₹40, here I have
life insurance coverage, here I have got
my disability news, and here I have got a
medical MB, in this way customized
policy is possible and this is with all the insurance
companies, so I want you to
call on Jal with your thoughts, understand that if the policy you have taken does
not have all the protection then
you
and after that the polish, then
just take care of the lighting and its  It is not sufficient,
you should take such a policy, 2 inches and
with it 20 World Cup Reduce Back Cover,
if you need to get any such presentation done
related to information, dress management
or portfolio management, financial
planning, insurance investment, you
can contact our team now, we give such
training, parents offer carpet presentation,
apart from this, these
videos have been made from training graduation, let us make it
absolutely clear once,
we are not endorsing any company's product or service, if
you like it,
Amit Paliwal's YouTube channel is there,
you can easily subscribe so that
you will keep getting such videos in future as well, the
number is given on this, Mr. and Mr. Satish
can contact on 90 1538, if
you need any information related to Inform Singh Sarpanch
or can get any such
presentation done, then this is all for today,
thank you very much Amit Paliwal